{
    "id": "a638dcc7bbfd41a28de40ec1edc4ac99",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Get",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I don't mind getting ................................ early if there is a good reason to.",
            "description": "To get up is to rise from bed after sleeping.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0ef4ede932e3422abfdea4d97c5688a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no room on the bus. Let's get ..................................... again.",
            "description": "To get off a vehicle is to leave a vehicle.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "in",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "75a6d2f390e0474d81d58be53865626e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Get ..................................... and I will drive you to the station.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8c2cbdd435364ca0a92b18e2b5a6a194"
        },
        {
            "question": "It took me a long time to get ......................................... the disappointment.",
            "description": "To get over is to overcome a difficulty.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "off",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "57bf74d17c584dccac4b094c4bfb6603"
        },
        {
            "question": "The robbers got ...................................... with diamonds worth millions of dollars.",
            "description": "To get away is to escape.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "away",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "799238e7a13b49208377bd9a935156b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The supervisor asked the employees to get ............................................... the job quickly.",
            "description": "To get on with work is to perform work.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "on with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e82ab0a24ddc4673928feee48af495fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "I tried calling but I couldn't get ............................................ to him.",
            "description": "To get through to somebody is to be able to talk to them via telephone.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "through",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8c3b1ca287f3413098285f1990f4ef05"
        },
        {
            "question": "I find it very difficult to get .......................................... on my meager salary.",
            "description": "To get by is to manage to live with great difficulty.",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b40f6c79a9cf49b2bc15194035fe849c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The setbacks got him ........................................",
            "description": "If something gets you down, it makes you very unhappy.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dbdc94af3c4f4562b01b2614e2a25fab"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can we get ........................................ for lunch on the weekend?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "together",
                "around"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c17a27772f840d7b33809648cd60db7"
        },
        {
            "question": "His stupidity got him ........................................... trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "through",
                "onto",
                "into"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "63ac5101ec6f417ab6def147b2655a2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rumors get ....................................... fast.",
            "description": "When rumors get around, they spread.",
            "answers": [
                "around",
                "over",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "313857f9bc2f4366902adc7d2c412eac"
        }
    ]
}